Previously on Children's Hospital.
We're going to have to evacuate
the hospital for 14 weeks.
However, I got us all a job as a
private contractor at
a Norman base in Japan.
But we're ambassadors, so no
betting on the operations.
Are you paying me to keep quiet while you
throw this surgery because
you bet money on it?
Uh-huh.
You doctors have been a
real asset to the base.
You got the pediatrics
clinic on its feet and
provided a lot of laughs along the way.
It's what we do.
How?
It's zingers like that that
I'm going to miss the most.
But now, you all have to go
back to Children's Hospital.
It's going to be nice
to get back to Brazil.
Yeah.
Which, as we all know, is where we were
based before we took this job in Japan.
Which is, as we also
know, where we've been.
And where we are.
This is Japan.
Owen, my stroke, you're under arrest.
Hey, what's going on?
Come on, man!
Owen!
You've been found guilty of colluding
with a criminal surgery fixing ring.
I hereby sentence you to five
years in a maximum security penitentiary.
By order of the Elder Council of Machines,
all females of childbearing
age shall surrender
to a birthing farm for one year.
What a bleak, dystopian
future we found ourselves in.
Thanks, guys.
Hit the lights!
I could never have written my first
speculative fiction
novel without you guys.
Hey, before you guys go,
listen, as you all know, my
boyfriend Owen gets out of prison
today, and he's been locked
up for five years, so
make him feel at home.
Oh, don't worry, Kat.
I have him scheduled for a
very difficult heart surgery today, so...
He hasn't performed surgery in five years.
I mean, how's that going to help?
In ways I couldn't possibly
describe without incriminating myself.
Hey, Kat, you know what Val and I
do when we feel out of place?
No.
We look at our award.
Have you guys seen this thing?
Fastest team tonsillectomy.
I mean, I don't know what
got into us that day.
It's like time to slow down.
I know a little something about that.
Owen's back!
Pack!
Owen's backpack is back!
Thanks for not ratting me out.
I'll make it up to you somehow.
Hey, where's my lady?
Kat, I've been back in
town for almost a minute.
Why aren't you riding this thing
in a supply closet right now?
Because I'm pregnant.
I've been standing behind
counters for seven months waiting
for the perfect time to tell you guys.
Owen, aren't you going to say anything?
I don't know what to say.
How about hello to your
unborn child saying?
Kat, I haven't seen you in five years.
What do you call the conjugal
visit we had seven months ago?
That never happened, so I call it fiction.
Oh, oh, what is that smell?
There he is.
Welcome back.
I'm so sorry.
We had to rezone your
office as a public fart
room, but you've always got
a place here at Children's.
Unless, of course, your
performance drops 4%, in
which time you're out on your ass.
It's corporate policy.
So have a good time.
Read a magazine.
Fart a little if you
got one in the chamber.
What a pleasure to see you back, huh?
4%.
Penny for your thoughts, my love.
Who ripped a blast in here?
Smells like broken promises to me, Kat.
No, it really smells like a bathroom.
How could you cheat on me
and claim that baby's mine?
How could you not remember?
We made love in a standalone
trailer like two wild animals.
I'll never forget what you said right
after your love exploded inside of me.
That one had a baby in it!
Why can't I remember?
Listen, are you okay to do that surgery?
It's in three hours.
I don't know, Kat.
I just don't.
Excuse me.
And excuse me again.
Listen, Owen, I think I can
finally make things right between us.
Check your hand.
Not interested.
Well, get interested.
Your big surgery's in two hours.
If you don't take a dive.
I can't handle this.
You sound just like you
did back in the joint.
Crying over your lack of
ability to handle stuff.
Dr. Ron Pippin, what's my
old cellmate doing here?
Still can't believe I shared a cell
with the only other doctor in lockup.
What a coincidence.
I don't believe in coincidences.
Then what are you doing here,
Pippin, if it's not a coincidence?
Just a remarkable concurrence of
circumstances without
any apparent connection.
See you around, pal.
Hey, there you are.
So glad you finally
remember our cultural visit.
I do?
Yes.
You said so an hour ago.
You even gave feedback on
color swatches for the nursery.
I think I'm losing my mind.
Oh, sorry.
She's all yours.
Oh.
Knock, knock.
Hey.
How you doing, buddy?
Yeah.
Okay?
But if I don't, Chief's gonna
kill me with her finger.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
You know what I do when I'm feeling blue?
I like to look at my award.
It's like time said...
Yeah, I know.
Time said something.
You guys took out some
tonsils really fast.
It's inspiring, really.
I'm glad you like it, because Val and I
would like to give it
to you as inspiration.
Okay.
Okay, so...
Now I have this.
You're welcome.
Excuse me.
Sorry, thought I was done farting, but
apparently farting isn't done with me.
Come on, man.
You're probably going to want to leave.
It's going to get pretty real in here.
Yeah, I don't need to be here for this.
Good luck on the surgery.
Thank you.
I guess I kind of oversold that.
You got this.
Owen, that doctor I've never seen before
has a dead ringer for you.
Cat, I'm Owen.
This is my former cellmate, Ron Pippin.
Looks like he's been pretending to be
me to have sex with you.
How could you do this, Pippin?
I just took advantage of
our uncanny resemblance.
Good luck in there, Owen.
Chief.
Is Madame Tussauds here?
I'm Owen.
What did you want?
I just had my finger sharpened.
If you don't throw this
surgery, you're dead.
Owen, if you don't ace
this surgery, you're dead.
Professionally speaking.
Over here, Si.
What?
You want me to say
anything to this mirror?
Okay.
Everybody get out.
I'm doing surgery.
Nurse, scalpel.
Remember, 4%.
You don't take a dive, you're dead.
If you don't ace this surgery,
you're out on your ass.
I just had my finger sharpened.
Okay, pacemaker is in place.
All we have to do now is turn it on.
Don't do it, Owen.
Chief, I'm no longer afraid of you.
Are you yes longer afraid of me?
Pippin, you're in on this too?
Finger in.
Let's finish this story.
The nightmare is finally
over for both of us.
Weird that you shared a jail cell with the
ringleader of the crime
you were busted for.
Sorry to put you through all of that.
I had no choice.
He had me by the balls.
Hey.
Look in your hand.
Oh, I love lemons and
strawberries and grapes.
Hey, Owen.
Now that we know this isn't your
baby, I mean, what do we do?
I would say for the next 13 weeks,
let's just try not to think about it.
Attention, staff.
Will all available doctors please
report to the emergency room?
That is all.
Well, that says let's
get back to work, huh?
Yep.
Ah, it's so good to be back
in the old United States of America.
Yeah, we're in Brazil.